# Mazhar Uddin

#### **ACCOUNT MANAGER**

A talented individual who has had a life long interests in Processing Claims, Processing Lodgments, Process Training to the new recruiters, Approving Pending Review Queues, Finding the errors committed by the Associates, Preparing Incentive data of the Associates. To seek a challenging career where I can show my technical and functional expertise and work towards the growth of the organization and to explore myself fully and realize my potential in this competitive world.

9873180803

**Q** Gurgaon, Haryana

in https://www.linkedin.com/feed/

#### **SKILLS**

Well presented Ability to communicate business

Problem solving concepts

Customer service Able to handle a team

# **EXPERIENCE**

## **Account Manager**

# Midland Credit Management Feb 2015 - Present

Ensuring the highest standards of quality and Responsible for operational efficiency and creating a relaxed environment where productivity and quality is second to none. Leading from the front & in charge of maintaining high levels of integrity and enforcing strict compliance.

- Help to Attorney's and Paralegal's to filed the suit against the consumer and get the judgment according to the outcomes
- Responsible for work quality and accuracy and ensure compliance with SLA's.
- Being a Training Maven train new folks and check their productivity and accuracy and share feedback on regular basis.

## **Process Associate**

## Genpact Jul 2011 - Nov 2014

Managing a high volume production time and improving to manage quality work. Also responsible for effectively developing, managing and leading the team to provide informative trainings.

- Being highly visible and the face of this business.
- Have handled a Team of 10 people & tracked their performance that includes their Productivity & accuracy targets.
- Responsible for work quality and accuracy and timely product delivery and ensure compliance with SLA's.
- Handle Customer call on daily basis from the clients and discuss the updates & accuracy
- Doing quality check on daily basis & provide feedback on for the same.

# **PROJECTS**

## Replacement Marketing

National Bearing Company Jul 2007 - Sep 2007

## Sales and Performance Analysis

Tableau Developer Oct 2020 - Oct 2020

#### **E-Commerce Sales Dashboard**

Business Analytics with Excel Mar 2022 - Mar 2022

## Company Product price and Sales data

## **EDUCATION**

**MBA** 

Cosmic Business School Jul 2006 - Aug 2008

Grauation

Shri Khandelwal Vaish P.G. College Feb 2003 - Mar 2005

12th

Government Senior Secondary School, Mahu Ibrahimpur Feb 2002 - Feb 2003

10th

Government Senior Secondary School, Mahu Ibrahimpur Feb 2000 - Mar 2001

## TRAINING CERTIFICATION

Time Management

Genpact 2014-04-05

**Customer Centricity** 

Midland Credit Management 2020-07-11

**Email Writing Skills Training** 

Midland Credit Management 2019-10-11

## **COURSES**

**Data Analyst** 

Simplilearn Oct 2020 - Mar 2022

## **LANGUAGES**

English Hindi Urdu

## **AWARDS**

#### Golden Award

Midland Credit Management 2019-02-11

For successfully completed on LC1 optimization project

Silver Award

Midland Credit Management 2021-08-15

For working on stuck accounts and covert those accounts to workable accounts

**Bronze Award** 

Genpact 2013-05-11

For achieveing outstanding performance in consecutive months

## **Bronze Award**

Midland Credit Management 2020-01-11

For Becoming Elite Club member for achieveing 100% quality and production for consecutive 6 months

HOBBIES		
Love to watch movies	Read Novels	Love to play cricket

# PERSONAL SKILLS

Hands on in Excel Working on visualization tools like Power BI and Tableau